JOSEPH E. PERSICO PAPERS (APAP030) 1910-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
Joseph E. Persico Papers1910-2003
nam_apap030
Persico, Joseph E.
18.54 4 films
The papers of Joseph Persico focus on his careers as a full-time author and as a political speechwriter for New York State Commissioner of Health, Hollis Ingraham, and New York State Governor, Nelson Rockefeller.
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
Selected Bibliography
My Enemy, My Brother: Men and Days of Gettsburg. New York: Viking Press, 1977.
Piercing the Reich: The Penetration of Nazi Germany by American Secret Agents during World War II. New York: Viking Press, 1979.
The Spiderweb, 1981
The Imperial Rockefeller: A Biography of Nelson A. Rockefeller. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1982.
Edward R. Murrow: An American Original. New York: McGraw-Hill, 1988.
Casey: From the OSS to the CIA. New York: Viking, 1990.
Nuremberg: Infamy on Trial. New York: Viking, 1994.
My American Journey. New York, NY: Random House, 1995. Co-authored with Colin Powell.
Roosevelt's Secret War: FDR and World War II Espionage. New York: Random House, 2001.
Eleventh Month, Eleventh Day, Eleventh Hour: Armistice Day, 1918, World War I and Its Violent Climax. New York, NY: Random House, 2004.
Biographical Sketch
Joseph E. Persico, author and former speechwriter for New York Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, was born to Thomas and Blanche Persico of Gloversville, New York, on July 19, 1930. In 1952, after receiving a BA in both English and Political Science from the New York State College for Teachers (as the University at Albany was then known), he entered the U.S. Navy and remained in the military for three years. Persico served as a Lieutenant Junior Grade aboard a minesweeper and also with NATO (North Atlantic Treaty Organization) Headquarters in Naples, Italy. Returning to the U.S. in 1956, Persico matriculated at Columbia University in New York for his graduate work.
In 1956, Joseph Persico began his political writing career, serving Governor W. Averell Harriman as a writer and researcher. After three years with Harriman, Persico then became a Foreign Service Officer for the United States Information Agency (USIA) working in Argentina, Brazil, and Washington. Between 1963 and 1966, Persico served as Executive Assistant to the New York State Health Commissioner, Hollis Ingraham. In 1966, Joseph Persico became the chief speechwriter for New York Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller. Continuing in this position for seven years, he remained Rockefeller's primary speechwriter as the Governor assumed the office of Vice President of the United States from 1974 to 1977.
In 1977, Joseph Persico transitioned into a full-time author, focusing on historical subjects. In that year, his Civil War piece, My Enemy My Brother: Men and Days of Gettysburg, was released. Two years later, he followed up this work with a novel, The Spiderweb, and a nonfiction study, Piercing the Reich: The Penetration of Nazi Germany by American Secret Agents During World War II. In 1982, Persico focused on Nelson Rockefeller's life and published the biography, The Imperial Rockefeller. During the 1990s, Persico created other historical works on both American espionage and the Nuremberg War Crimes Trials following World War II. These works were Casey: From the OSS to the CIA and Nuremberg: Infamy on Trial. Persico also targeted renowned broadcast journalist Edward R. Murrow for a biographical sketch in 1990. In addition to his books, Persico has also published numerous articles on American history.
Persico collaborated with former Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff and later Secretary of State, Colin L. Powell, on his biography. Between 1994 and 1996, the author developed a personal relationship with his subject, occasionally addressing Powell as "Sir Colin", and "Mon General", from "The Hired Pen". Joseph Persico continues to publish books on historical subjects. In November 2001, Random House Inc. released Roosevelt's Secret War: FDR and World War II Espionage and in 2004, Eleventh Month, Eleventh Day, Eleventh Hour: Armistice Day, 1918, World War I and Its Violent Climax was published.
Apart from his professional career, Joseph Persico's private life has been spent with his wife, Sylvia La Vista Persico, and his children, Vanya and Andrea. He currently lives in Guilderland, N.Y.
Chronological Index to Press Releases, Speeches, and Transcripts Written for Nelson A. Rockefeller
This index was transcribed from the handwritten original provided by the donor covering the years 1964-1976.
1964
1964 July 14 San Francisco, CA, Text of Remarks, Republication National Convention
1964 July 17 San Francisco, CA, Press Release, Statement by Nelson A. Rockefeller
1964 August 12 Albany, NY, Press Release, Statement by Nelson A. Rockefeller
1965
1965 September 28 Albany, NY, Draft of Speech, Health, Education & Welfare
1965 October 21 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Roswell Park Memorial
1966
1966 May 17 New York City, NY, WCBS-TV
1966 May 24 Albany, NY, Excerpts, 62nd Annual Health Conference
1966 August 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, President Zalaman Shazar of Israel
1966 August 4 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Port Authority Loan Bill
1966 August 10 Canandaigua, NY, Press Release, Ontario County Republicans
1966 August 11 Speculator, NY, Press Release, Hamilton County
1966 August 11 Saratoga Springs, NY, Press Release, Saratoga County Republicans
1966 August 11 Glens Falls, NY, Excerpts, Rotary Club
1966 August 14 Middletown, NY, Press Release, Orange County Students
1966 August 16 Williamsville, NY, Press Release, Amherst Republicans
1966 August 17 Niagara Falls, NY, Excerpt, Polish Union of America
1966 August 22 Garden City, NY, Press Release, Nassau County Republicans
1966 August 23 Lake Placid, NY, Press Release, Potato Seed
1966 August 23 Malone, NY, Press Release, Kiwanis Club Lumchem
1966 August 24 Pike, NY, Press Release, Massive Aid to Education
1966 August 24 Alexander, NY, Press Release, Genesee County Republicans
1966 August 25 Watkins Glen, NY, Press Release, Schuyler County Republicans
1966 August 26 Bath, NY, Press Release, Steuben County Town Offices
1966 August 25 Hornell, NY, Press Release, Board of Education
1966 August 25 Hornell, NY, Excerpts of Address, Hornell Union Park
1966 August 26 Easton, NY, Press Release, Washington County Fair
1966 August 30 New York City, NY, Excerpt, Suffolk County Convention
1966 August 31 Speculator, NY, Press Release, Moffett Beach
1966 September 1 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts of Remarks, State Fair Grounds
1966 September 2 Chatham, NY, Press Release, Columbia County Fair
1966 September 2 Schaghticoke, NY, Press Release, Rensselaer County Fair
1966 September 9 Lake George, NY, Excerpts, Press Association
1966 September 9 Seneca Falls, NY, Press Release, Republican Perception
1966 September 9 Auburn, NY, Press Release, Cayuga County Young Republicans
1966 September 12 Lake Ronkonkoma, NY, Excerpt, Long Island Railroad Turbine Car
1966 September 12 Huntington, NY, Press Release, Suffolk County Republicans
1966 September 13 Kiamesha Lake, NY, Excerpt, New York County Officers Association
1966 September 13 Kiamesha Lake, NY, Excerpt, Association of Real Estate Boards
1966 September 14 Syracuse, NY, Excerpt, State Council of Churches
1966 September 20 Endicott, NY, Press Release, Endicott High School
1966 September 21 New York City, NY, Excerpt, International Bridge
1966 September 21 Staten Island, NY, Excerpt, Willowbrook State School
1966 September 21 New York City, NY, Excerpt, Career Development
1966 September 27 North Castle, NY, Press Release, Byram Hills High School
1966 September 28 Yonkers, NY, Press Release, Cross County Shopping Center
1966 September 28 Oneonta, NY, Press Release, State College Oneonta
1966 September 28 Albany, NY, Press Release, D.E. Button Testimonial
1966 September 29 Willsville, NY, Press Release, Republican Lunch
1966 September 30 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Israel Cummings Lecture
1966 September 30 Dunkirk, NY, Press Release, Chautauqua County
1966 October 1 New York City, Excerpt, Salute to Women Lunch
1966 October 1 Long Island, NY, Press Release, Job Development Authority
1966 October 2 Mahopac, NY, Excerpt, Putman County Republic
1966 October 6 Morrisville, NY, Excerpt, State University College
1966 October 6 Hamilton, NY, Excerpts, C.A. Dana Creative Arts Center
1966 October 7 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, New York State Library Association
1966 October 7 Camillus, NY, Press Release, Camillus Republican Committee
1966 October 11 Hempstead, NY, Excerpts, Hofstra University
1966 October 11 Mineola, NY, Excerpts, Supreme Court Building
1966 October 11 Long Island, NY, Press Release, Nassau County Tour
1966 October 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Garment Center Congregation
1966 October 14 New York City, NY, Excerpt, Al Smith Dinner
1966 October 15 Bronx, NY, Excerpts, Youth Opportunity Center
1966 October 17 Suffern, NY, Excerpt, Pilot Guidance Center
1966 October 17 Tallman, NY, Press Release, Rescue Hudson River
1966 October 18 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, Rotary Club
1966 October 19 Lewis County, NY, Press Release, Dairy Industry
1966 October 19 Fulton, NY, Press Release, Oswego County Republicans
1966 October 22 New York City, NY, Excerpts, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
1966 October 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Columbia Association
1966 October 24 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Nation Day
1966 October 26 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Flatbush Mental Clinic
1966 October 28 New York City, NY, Press Release, Frank O'Connor
1966 October 28 New York City, NY, Statement, Narcotic Program
1966 October 29 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Bridge Street Church
1966 October 30 Bronx, NY, Excerpts, Pre Election Rally
1966 October 31 Bronx, NY, Excerpt, Concourse Plaza Rally
1966 November 1 Buffalo, NY, Press Release, Cazenovia Creek
1966 November 1 Brooklyn, NY, Press Release, Brooklyn Borough
1966 November 3 White Plains, NY, Remarks, General Foods
1966 November 3 Garden City, NY, Remarks, Nassau County Committee Meeting
1966 November 2 White Plains, NY, Excerpts, New York State Identification and Intelligence
1966 November 4 Pleasantville, NY, Excerpts, Republican Rally
1966 November 5 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Manhattan Center Rally
1967
1967 October 4 Albany, NY, Press Release, Constitutional Convention
1968
1968 January 1 Albany, NY, Press Release, New York State Legislative Women's Forum
1968 January 11 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Agricultural Society
1968 January 16 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Association of Mental Health
1968 January 27 New York City, NY, New York State District Attorneys Associations
1968 January 29 Albany, NY, Excerpts, 27th Armored Division
1968 January 29 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Traffic Safety
1968 January 31 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Conference on Air Pollution
1968 February 2 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Mall Project
1968 February 7 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Veterans of Foreign War
1968 February 8 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Employees Brotherhood
1968 February 14 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Hospitals and Nursing Homes
1968 February 18 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Regarding Crime
1968 February 19 Albany, NY, Press Conference, Taylor Law
1968 February 21 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Renewing Cities
1968 February 22 New York City, NY, Excerpts, NYU School of Medicine
1968 February 26 Albany, NY, Excerpts, League of Women Voters
1968 February 27 Albany, NY, Press Conference, Red Room Capitol
1968 February 27 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, New York State Urban Development
1968 March 4 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Air and Water Pollution
1968 March 6 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Urban Development Corporation
1968 March 6 Albany, NY, Press Release, New York State Broadcasters
1968 March 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Legal Aid Society
1968 March 12 Pittsburgh, PN, Excerpts, 3rd Annual Conference on Urban Transportation
1968 March 12 Brighten, NY, Excerpts, Rochester Times Union
1968 March 20 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Health Security Act
1968 March 21 New York City, NY, Statement, Withdrawal from Presidential Campaign
1968 March 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Racial Justice New York Community
1968 March 22 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Jewish Appeal
1968 March 25 New York City, NY, Press Release, Executive Budget 1968-1969
1968 March 29 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Budget
1968 April 4 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Protestant Welfare Agencies
1968 April 5 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Conference on Youth
1968 April 5 New York City, NY, Address, Before Conference on Youth
1968 April 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Honoring Harry Van Arsdale, Jr.
1968 April 8 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Urban Development
1968 April 10 Washington, D.C., Testimony, Senate Committee on Public Works
1968 April 11 New York City, NY, Excerpts, National Planning Association
1968 April 18 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, Society of Newspaper Editions
1968 April 24 Washington, D.C., Testimony, Riding Hospital Cost
1968 April 24 Washington, D.C., Testimony, Rivers and Harbors
1968 May 1 Philadelphia, PA, Excerpts, World Affairs Council of Philadelphia
1968 May 2 Iowa City, IA, Excerpts, University of Iowa
1968 May 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Conference on Aging
1968 May 4 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Electric Power
1968 May 7 Albany, NY, Special Message to Legislature, Human Rights
1968 May 8 Minnesota, MN, Excerpts, University of Minnesota
1968 May 9 Lawrence, KA, Excerpts, University of Kansas
1968 May 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Drug Abuse Prevention
1968 May 20 Gainesville, FL, Excerpts, University of Florida
1968 May 22 Albany, NY, Press Release, Medical Care
1968 May 22 Detroit, MI, Excerpts, Economic Club
1968 May 23 Atlanta, GA, Excerpt, Spelman College
1968 May 24 Atlanta, GA, Excerpt, Emory College
1968 May 28 Denver, CO, Excerpt, University of Denver
1968 May 29 Salt Lake City, UT, Excerpt, University of Utah
1968 June 3 Portland, OR, Address, Republican National Convention
1968 June 3 Milwaukee, WI, Excerpts, Canaan Baptist Church
1968 June 10 Meadville, PA, Excerpt, Allegheny College
1968 June 11 Washington, D.C., Press Release, National Press Club
1968 June 12 Los Angeles, CA, Press Release, Address to Town Hall
1968 June 13 San Francisco, CA, Press Release, Commonwealth Club
1968 June 19 Cleveland, OH, Excerpts, Public Square
1968 June 20 Lorain, OH, Excerpt, Lorain County Fundraising
1968 June 20 Chicago, IL, Excerpt, The Loop
1968 June 25 Albany, NY, Press Release, Federal Fiscal Policies
1968 June 26 New Haven, CT, Press Release, Urban Redevelopment
1968 June 27 Hartford, CT, Excerpt, Fundraising Dinner
1968 June 28 Lincoln, NE, Excerpt, University of Nebraska
1968 June 28 South Dakota, Excerpt, Fundraising Dinner
1968 June 30 San Antonio, TX, Excerpt, Lulac Convention
1968 July 8 San Francisco, CA, Excerpts, New Leadership
1968 July 12 Watertown, NY, Excerpts, Thousand Island Bridge
1968 July 13 New York City, NY, Press Release, Peace in Vietnam
1968 July 13 New York City, NY, Statement, Program for Peace Vietnam
1968 July 16 Springfield, IL, Excerpts, Illinois House of Representatives
1968 July 26 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, International Platform Association
1968 September 11 White Plains, NY, Excerpts, Rally for Richard Nixon
1968 September 15 Worthington, MN, Excerpt, Turkey Day Celebration
1968 September 15 St. Cloud, MN, Excerpt, Rally for John M. Zwach
1968 October 3 Tarrytown, NY, Excerpt, Women for Nixon Nakasian
1968 October 3 Poughkeepsie, NY, Excerpt, Rotary Club
1968 October 3 Schenectady, NY, Rally for Dan Butten
1968 October 4 Newburgh, NY, Excerpt, Urban Development Corp
1968 October 4 St Louis, MO, Excerpt, Rally Curtis Crawford
1968 October 4 Kansas City, KS, Excerpt, Reception for R. Harman
1968 October 5 Kansas City, MO, Excerpt, GOP Fund Raiser
1968 October 8 Buffalo, NY, Excerpt, Nixon Rally
1968 October 9 Kiamesha Lake, NY, Excerpt, County Officers Association
1968 October 12 New York City, NY, Excerpt, Columbus Day Dinner
1968 October 16 New York City, NY, Excerpt, Public Employment Relations
1968 October 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Republican Candidates
1968 October 17 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Health Planning Council
1968 October 17 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Al Smith Memorial Dinner
1968 October 18 Whitney Point, NY, Excerpt, North South Expressway
1968 October 18 New York City, NY, Press Release, Lotos Club
1968 October 18 New York City, NY, Excerpt, Mt. Sinai Medical School
1968 October 23 Wilmington, DE, Excerpt, GOP Candidate
1968 October 23 Silver Springs, MD, Excerpt, Mathias for Senate
1968 October 23 Clinton, IA, Excerpts, Tom Rily for Congress
1968 October 23 Newton IA, Excerpts, Robert D. Ray for Governor
1968 October 24 Davenport, IA, Excerpts, Republican Candidates
1968 October 24 New York City, Excerpt, United Nations Day
1968 October 28 Jamaica, NY, Excerpt, Long Island Railroad
1968 October 29 Stamford, CT, Excerpt, Senior Citizen Reception
1968 October 29 Hartford, CT, Excerpt, Ladd for Congress
1968 October 30 Syracuse, NY, Excerpt, Richard Nixon
1968 October 31 Philadelphia, PA, Excerpt, Republican City Committee
1968 October 31 Buffalo, NY, Excerpt, University at Buffalo
1968 November 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Madison Square Garden
1968 November 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Senator Jacob Javits
1968 November 25 Bronx, NY, Excerpts, Dedication Co-op City
1968 December 6 Palm Springs, CA, Excerpts, State and Local Relations in Health, Education, and Welfare Federal Aid
1968 December 6 New York City, Excerpts Remarks by Malcom Wilson
1968 December 6 New Orleans, LA, Excerpts, Annual Congress of Cities
1968 December 11 New York City, NY, Excerpts, M. Legexdre Dinner
1968 December 11 Staten Island, Excerpts, Chamber of Commerce
1968 December 17 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Testimonial for Rev. J. Mark
1968 December 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
1969
1969 January 2 New York City, Excerpts, Swearing-in Ceremony of Supreme Court Justices
1969 January 14 New York City, Remarks, Dinner for President Lyndon Johnson
1969 January 16 Syracuse, NY, Statement, Dean Charles Cornell Century Farm Citations
1969 January 24 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Narcotic Addiction Control Commission
1969 January 27 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 1968 USO Woman of the Year Award Dinner
1969 January 28 Albany, Press Conference, WMHT Program Press Capitol Report
1969 January 29 Endicott, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Endicott Johnson Plant
1969 January 29 New York City, NY, Remarks, Dinner Honoring Spyros Skouras
1969 January 31 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Institute of Planners Conference
1969 February 4 Albany, NY, Press Release, Hugh Morrow as Director of Communications
1969 February 5 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Annual Legislative Dinner
1969 February 5 Albany, NY, Excerpts, 6th Annual Legislative Assembly
1969 February 11 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Annual Meeting of the Association of Fire Districts
1969 February 12 Springfield, IL, Excerpts, Annual Abraham Lincoln Association Dinner
1969 February 12 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Revenue Sharing
1969 February 13 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Revenue Sharing
1969 February 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York County Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner
1969 February 17 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Albany County Republican Committee Dinner
1969 February 19 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Revenue Redistribution/Federal Aid
1969 March 7 New York City, NY, Press Release, Speech to Commerce and Industry Association
1969 March 15 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, National Alliance of Businessmen Conference
1969 April 10 Philadelphia, PA, Excerpts, Delaware River Basin Commission
1969 April 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Press Conference Announcing Plans for Battery Park
1969 April 18 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York City Building Trades Employers Association
1969 April 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Interracial Council for Business Opportunity
1969 May 2 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 8th Annual Governors Conference on Aging
1969 May 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, St. Patrick's Cathedral
1969 May 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 14th Annual Senator Wagner Memorial Dinner
1969 May 22 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 150th Anniversary Luncheon of New York Savings Bank
1969 May 26 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Management Association Conference
1969 May 28 New York City, NY, Citizens Committee on the Problems of Alcohol
1969 June 8 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Presidents Commission on Income Maintenance Programs
1969 June 10 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, Consolidation and Intergovernmental Cooperation Act of 1969 Federal Aid
1969 June 13 Troy, NY, Excerpts, Commencement Exercises at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute
1969 June 18 New York City, NY, Statement, Hudson River Water Pollution Enforcement Conference
1969 August 2 Blue Mountain Lake, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Adirondack Museum
1969 August 8 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Governor's Day Luncheon
1969 August 28 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Annual State Farm Dinner
1969 August 28 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Empire Court State Fair
1969 September 2 Colorado Springs, CO, Excerpts, National Governors Conference
1969 September 5 Middletown, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Polytherm Plastics
1969 September 5 Poughkeepsie, NY, Press Release, Regarding Economic Growth in New York State
1969 September 8 New York City, NY, Excerpts, International Union of Amalgamated Transit
1969 September 10 Bronx, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking of North Bronx Hospital
1969 September 10 Kiamesha Lake, NY, Excerpts, New York County Officers Association
1969 September 11 Brooklyn, NY, Press Release, Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce
1969 September 17 Williamsburg, VA, Excerpts, Council of Appalachian Governors
1969 September 18 Albany, NY, Press Release, Schoharie County Republican Reception
1969 September 19 Lake Placid, NY, Excerpts, Associated Industries of New York State
1969 September 23 Hempstead, NY, Press Release, Long Island Association
1969 September 25 Lake Placid, NY, Excerpts, Arthur Godfrey Award Presentation
1969 September 25 Lake Placid, NY, Excerpts, New York State Conservation Council
1969 September 30 Buffalo, NY, Press Release, Buffalo Area Chamber of Commerce
1969 October 5 Garden City, NY, Excerpts, Nassau County Weekly Press Association Dinner
1969 October 6 New York City, NY, 74th Convention of the American Osteopathic Association
1969 October 6 Purchase, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking Ceremony at SUNY Purchase
1969 October 9 Interlake, NY, Excerpts, 100th Anniversary of Willard State Hospital
1969 October 9 Oswego, NY, Excerpts, Nine Mile Point Nuclear Power Plant
1969 October 10 Albany, NY, Press Release, Albany County Republican Committee
1969 October 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner
1969 October 17 Fredonia, NY, Excerpts, Dedication and Convocation at SUNY Fredonia
1969 October 18 Corning, NY, Press Release, Steuben County Republican Dinner
1969 October 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Nations Day Observance
1969 October 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers
1969 October 23 Buffalo, NY, Excerpt, New York State Building and Construction Trades Council
1969 October 27 Buffalo, NY, Press Release, AFL-CIO Convention
1969 October 28 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, New York State School Boards Association
1969 October 28 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Association of Housing and Urban Renewal
1969 October 28 Utica, NY, Press Release, Utica Chamber of Commerce
1969 October 29 Norwich, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Georgia Pacific Plant